结论：
It's a compromise between safety and ease of use.  If the user has visited the site before and the download is in response to a user click, it's likely (not definite :-{, but likely) that the download is wanted.  Contrawise, if we warn on every download of every file that might have executable code in it, we get a lot of people upset (usually about PDF downloads).  For many downloads, our safebrowsing checksum checks will warn about known malware. 

It's not anything like perfect protection, but it's the best we could come up with in this space.


翻译：
这是一个安全性和易用性之间的妥协。如果用户访问网站之前,应对用户点击下载,很可能(不明确:- {,但很有可能),下载想要的。Contrawise,如果我们提醒每一个下载文件,可能有可执行代码,我们得到很多人沮丧(通常约PDF下载)。对于许多下载,我们safebrowsing校验和检查将警告已知恶意软件。 


这不是像完美的保护,但这是最好的我们可以想出在这个空间